Who?
Dong Hwa's brother.
Heo Dong Jin.
Darn you, why are you
playing such a sick joke?
What are you talking about?
Jeez, you're a lunatic.
Dong Jin died last year.
You've gone too far
with your jokes, you punk.
Don't you know
Dong Hwa's still messed up over that?
Did you see a ghost or something?
Who were you staying with?
Why haven't you reported anything?
What happened to Chu Tae Jeong?
I'm sorry.
He left the house this morning.
Is that so? Then why didn't you
report it immediately?
I was preoccupied
trying to find the cell phone. I'm sorry.
"Preoccupied"?
There wasn't anything else going on?
He's a cop after all.
You can't leave any room for him to doubt.
He'd come back with even an ounce of doubt.
If he does come back, what do I do?
We have to kill him.
Isn't it obvious?
If he does come back,
it means he doubts who you really are.
Even though he's a cop,
we'll have no option but to get rid of him.
We need to finish this quickly,
so find the cell phone first.
Understood.
[Dong Hwa, I'm arriving soon.
I saw your brother. When are you returning?]
[Why aren't you replying?]
[But Dong Jin... Why is he so cute?
It makes me want to tease him.]
[Dong Hwa, reply when you see this.
Nothing's wrong, right?]
[But Dong Jin... Why is he so cute?
It makes me want to tease him.]
You're all right, aren't you?
Huh?
Anyway, I don't know why
you're making such sick jokes,
but let me know when you hear from Dong Hwa.
Chul Jin, we should head back now.
Tae Jeong, I have to go.
Let's talk more
when you come into work next week.
Oh, by the way,
don't go around stirring things up
in Dongcheon in the meantime.
You need solid evidence
to make a case, understand?
Forget about what happened 10 years ago.
I'm going now.
Are you Dong Jin?
No?
You're Dong Jin, right?
Are you really Dong Jin?
Where does Dong Hwa sleep?
What?
It seems like this house
only has one bedroom.
If he wasn't Dong Jin,
who in the world was he?
You wouldn't know the loneliness
of eating alone, would you?
I do.
How do you know?
When I was young,
I spent a lot of time alone too.
Investigate it thoroughly.
Huh?
You said it's important to you.
Did you enjoy the smoke?
What? Still not ready to tell me?
Get up. Stop pretending.
Hey, Heo Dong Hwa.
Heo Dong Hwa!
Darn it.
Gosh, where is it?
You shouldn't kill me yet.
Chu Tae Jeong?
Dong Jin, you are home.
Yeah.
Dong Jin died last year.
Who were you staying with?
Anyway, what are you doing here?
I'm asking why you came back.
I was worried about you.
You were sick last night,
but I left without checking on you
in the morning.
I'm fine now.
If he does come back,
it means he doubts who you really are.
Even though he's a cop,
we'll have no option but to get rid of him.
By the way, you haven't heard from Dong Hwa?
No.
What were you doing?
Is something wrong?
Dong Jin.
I missed you.
You're going to stay here today, right?
Is that okay?
Are you going somewhere?
I need to go take care of something.
Get some rest.
Spare me, please?
- Let me live. Please.
- Just tell me where the phone is.
You can't escape now.
But if I tell you, you're going to kill me.
I can... I can help you quit that job, okay?
Enough money to live anywhere and never
have to work another day in your life...
I'll give that to you, okay?
Do you think you're in any position
to bargain with me?
Stop talking nonsense.
Tae Jeong's a cop.
He saw your face.
He also knows I disappeared.
At this rate,
it's only a matter of time
before you get caught.
Kill me. Kill me!
If you kill me, it'd only hurt you.
So, don't complicate things
any further and think carefully.
You want a fresh start too, don't you?
I said I will help you.
Why does he have so much cash?
Who is he really?
If you're not going to tell me
where the phone is, forget it.
Where are you going? Hey! Hey!
Gosh, darn it.
So, don't complicate things
any further and think carefully.
You want a fresh start too, don't you?
You wait here.
I'll handle Min Ho myself.
Should we leave now?
Aren't you hungry?
No, I'm not very hungry yet.
How about some sushi?
You know Yukari in Cheongdam-dong?
A third-generation sushi chef
from Japan will be serving there
as a special guest chef for just one week.
Don't you want to go try it?
Sure. Should we go there then?
You and Min Ho...
are from the same orphanage, right?
How long have you known each other?
It's been about 15 years.
Are you feeling down
because an old friend died?
No, not at all.
Why do you think Min Ho died?
Because he failed to eliminate the target.
"Why couldn't he kill the target?"
I thought about it.
I think it was because he was a good person.
That's why he wanted to start fresh
with the woman he was supposed to kill.
How stupid.
That target will come
to the Japanese restaurant.
You can handle it, right?
Yes.
Because you're different from Min Ho.
An art tube...
Why are you touching what's not yours?
I'm sorry.
I was curious what drawing tools you use.
It's quite heavy.
I guess you have a lot of tools.
Can you draw me too?
What?
Please draw me too.
I...
Can I move?
No.
But my body feels stiff.
That happens to everyone at first.
You'll be fine after some time passes.
I think it'd be okay
if I moved just a little.
Keep your gaze.
Don't look this way.
Are you nervous?
Your heart's racing, you know?
Maybe it's because your neck is slim.
It makes it obvious.
Dong Jin.
Don't you miss Leo?
Who?
Leo. Your family's dog.
Oh yes, Leo.
When did Leo die?
I don't know. I don't remember.
Can I ask you a question?
Who are you?
The dog that Dong Hwa's family raised
wasn't named Leo, but Logan.
Dong Jin personally named the dog.
There's no way he wouldn't know the name.
I heard Dong Jin died last year.
Didn't you know?
Who are you?
Why are you in this house?
Then what about you?
Why did you come back to this house?
Isn't this exactly the kind of thing
you can report to the police?
That someone's pretending
to be your friend's brother.
You're right.
I'm not Heo Dong Jin.